Guide to the Cornell Information Technologies records,1940-2009.
Cornell Information Technologies Records
- Manuals Contributed by John W. Rudan (Box 43)
  - CUPL - The Cornell University Programming Language (R. J. Walker), 1966-12
  - CUPL - The Cornell University Programming Language (R. J. Walker), 1967-07
    With Instructions and Assignments for Statistics 407 taught by John W. Rudan, Fall 1969
  - Operations Guide for IBM 3270 Display Systems from Larry Fresinksi, 1973-05
- Manuals Contributed by David W. Pulleyn (Box 43)
  - Reference Manual IBM 29 Card Punch, 1965
  - Reference Manual IBM 557 Alphabetic Interpreter, 1963
  - IBM 82, 83, 84 Sorters Product Reference, 1965
  - IBM 24 Card Punch, 26 Printing Card Punch Ops Manual, 1958
  - IBM 1403 Printers - Field Engineering - Theory of Operrations, 1967
  - IBM 1403 Printers - Field Engineering - Instruction/Maintenance, 1965
  - IBM 1403 Printers - Field Engineering - Maintenance Manual, 1966
  - IBM 1403 Printers - Form Design Considerations (several), 1964
  - IBM 1403 Printer Component Description, 1971
  - IBM 1403N1 Printers - Operator's Guide, 1967
  - New IBM Document Processing System 9360 Sales Blurb
  - IBM Information Records Division - Record Systems Review vol2/#2
  - IBM IBM 87 Collator Control Panel Design (2 actual board designs)
  - IBM Data Processing Cards - General Purpose Card Samples
- MDM/MPM System Reference, 1986 (Box 44)
- MDM System Manager's Reference, 1988 (Box 44)
- Minidisk Manager Messages and Codes, 1988 (Box 44)
- Minidisk Manager Operator Reference, 1988 (Box 44)
- MDM Subpool Manager's Reference, 1988 (Box 44)
- Minidisk Manager's User's Reference, 1988 (Box 44)
- Minidisk Manager Summary Command Briefs, 1986 (Box 44)
  Subpool Manager, System Manager, General User
- Wheels for the Mind - Apple University Consortium, 1985-1988 (Box 44)
- Hewlett-Packard (HP) Advertising Kit (Vectra, Portable Plus), 1984-1985 (Box 44)
- Microcomputer and Component Price Lists(NetComm and MOS), 1986-89 (Box 44)
- Plan for MOS Inventory Management System, 1986-06 (Box 44)
- IBM Advertising PC Sales (Fairs, etc), 1986 (Box 44)
- Controversy on PC Sales on Campus (local merchants complain), 1984 (Box 44)
- Radio Adverising PC Sales promos (WVBR), 1986-1987 (Box 44)
- PC (Microcomp) Sales - Legal Issues, Contracts, etc, 1983-1984 (Box 44)
- Choosing a Microcomputer and Components Guides, 1985-1986 (Box 44)
- Apple News, Emails, etc, 1984 (Box 44)
- Organizing for PC Sales and Support at CCS, 1984 (Box 44)
- Apple Corp - Delivering the Campus Microcomputer, 1986 (Box 44)
  A Planning Guide
- Micromputer Sales and Support - Miscellaneous Issues, 1984 (Box 44)
- Apple AD slicks, 1984 (Box 44)
- Desktop Publishing Forums, etc, 1986 (Box 44)
- Macintosh Advertising, 1985-1989 (Box 44)
- Campus Store - Micro sales (software, etc), 1987 (Box 44)
- Letters to Incoming Students re PCs, 1984-1986 (Box 44)
- Special PC Sales Promotions to Graduating Seniors, 1986 (Box 44)
- Office Equipment Center (OEC) Catalog of Services, 1983 (Box 44)
- Apple/Macintosh Promo Literature, 1984 (Box 44)
- MOS - Microcomputers and Office Systems - Beginnings, promo, etc, 1987 (Box 44)
  MOS resulted from Merger of OEC and CCS Computer Sales
- MOS resulted from Merger of OEC and CCS Computer Sales (Box 44)
- IBM - Campus Communications - An Executive Perspective (wkshop), 1988 (Box 44)
- CCS Workshop Announcements (spring/fall), 1983 (Box 44)
- Policy on Software Support - Doug Gale to CCS Staff (preview), 1982 (Box 44)
  Also includes the 1985 Official Policy
- Guidelines for Buying Computers (Policy), 1970-1980 (Box 44)
- University Unions - Office Info Systems Study, etc, 1984 (Box 44)
- Academic Computing - Gordon Galloway Director Misc Correspondence, 1982 (Box 44)
- Academic Computing - Alec Grimison (acting Dir) Misc Correspondence, 1981 (Box 44)
- CUINFO Usage Stats and Miscellaneous Memos, 1985-1987 (Box 44)
- CUThesis Usage, 1985 (Box 44)
- Data Dictionaries and System descriptions
- Data Dictionaries, Systems Descriptions from 1970's (Compiled by Lynne K. Personius) (Box 45)
  - System Descriptions
  - Program Definitions
  - Student Records Program Definitions I
  - Student Records Program Definitions II
  - Student Records Data Dictionary
  - Student Financial System Data Dictionary
  - Library Acquisitions Data Dictionary
  - Payroll/Personnel Data Dictionary
  - Admissions Data Dictionary
  - Public Affairs Data Dictionary
- Data Dictionaries, Systems Descriptions from 1970's (Compiled by Lynne K. Personius) (Box 46)
  - Program and File Log Sheets
  - Program Definitions
  - GCA Data Dictionary
  - File Narratives
  - Motor Vehicles Data Dictionary
  - College Stores Data Dictionary
  - Facilities Inventory Data Dictionary
  - VM Scheduler - Cornell Design (Robert D. Cowles), 1976-1978
  - VM Scheduler - White Paper (Robert D. Cowles), 1976
  - CMS Tutorial (Colleen Wells), 1982
  - Cornell CP and CMS Command Reference (Colleen Wells), 1982
  - Introduction to CMS
  - Waterloo Script Reference Manual (Colleen Wells), 1980
  - Script Users Guide (Colleen Wells), 1981
- AIX Materials
- AIX Joint Study - VS Fortran (M. Pottle), 1989-05 (Box 47)
- AIX Review Meeting (status, etc), 1990-04 (Box 47)
- AIX Review Meeting (status, etc), 1990-12 (Box 47)
- Cornell IAX/370 Requirements and Project Groups, 1989-11 (Box 47)
- AIX Project Chairs Meeting Notes, 1989-09 (Box 47)
- AIX Project Plans for 1991, 1990-08 (Box 47)
- AIX Technical Issues (UBC AIX Workshop notes and others), 1990 (Box 47)
- AIX Accounting System Req's, Backup, ReelLihrarian etc, 1990 (Box 47)
- AIX Joint Study - Workstation/Supercomputer Integration, 1989-1990 (Box 47)
- AIX Work Teams/Plans, etc, 1989 (Box 47)
- AIX Project Review Meeting, 1989-07 (Box 47)
- AIX Project Review Meeting, 1989-09 (Box 47)
- AIX Project Review Meeting, 1990-02 (Box 47)
- AIX Project Review Meeting, 1990-12 (Box 47)
- IBM AIX Glossy across systems and products, 1989 (Box 47)
- AIX Issues, etc (covering a whole range of issues), 1991 (Box 47)
- AIX Steering Committee (notes, etc), 1990 (Box 47)
- AIX Steering Committee (notes, etc), 1991 (Box 47)
- IBM Joint Study - AIX Enhancements, 1992 (Box 47)
- AIX Project "Buzz" (misc background emails), 1989-1990 (Box 47)
- AIX Project "Buzz" (misc background emails), 1991-1992 (Box 47)
- AIX Project "Buzz" (plans, proposals, issues, etc), 1991 (Box 47)
- AIX Project "Buzz" (misc background emails), 1992 (Box 47)
- AIX Slides for Presentation to Janet Early (IBM Honcho), 1992-02 (Box 47)
- CNSF SMART Node Newsletters, 1992 (Box 47)
- AIX Project Judy Warren Notes, 1989 (Box 47)
- CNSF Migration from CMS to AIX, 1991 (Box 47)
- CNSF Migration from AIX to AIX/ESA, 1991 (Box 47)
- AIX/PAIX/AIX370 Communications with Frank Tung, 1992 (Box 47)
- Supercomputing AIX Consortium (organization, etc), 1991 (Box 47)
- Supercomputing AIX Consortium (organization, etc), 1992 (Box 47)
- Supercomputing AIX Status Reports (from meeting), 1992 (Box 47)
- Supercomputing AIX (Gordon Wright, IBM Mgr stuff), 1992 (Box 47)
- CNSF - SSI system, 1991 (Box 47)
- CNSF - KSR1 system, 1991 (Box 47)
- NCSA PR Materials, 1990 (Box 47)
- CNSF - IBM Market Solutions Meeting (Superstorage/ABH), 1990 (Box 47)
- Meeting Notes. JW Rudan and Dave Lambert (includes 95-96 budget), 1995 (Box 48)
- Meeting Notes. JW Rudan and Dave Lambert, 1994 (Box 48)
- Lambert Items - Miscellaneous, Buzz, etc, 1989 (Box 48)
- 120 Maple Ave - Planning, Design, 1995 (Box 48)
- OIT Space Committee Reports (Box 48)
  - An Analysis of Space Needs Through 1993, 1990-11
  - An Analysis of Space Needs through 1993 with Projections Through the Year 2000, 1992-01
  - CIT Space Requirements - Overheads Summary
- Re-engineering Retreat Evaluation, 1996 (Box 48)
- IR Budget and supporting materials, 1993-1994 (Box 48)
- ASDT - Transition from IR and DT (Helen Mohrmann Director), 1996-1997 (Box 48)
- IR/ASDT Budgets and Helen Mohrmann materials, 1995-1996 (Box 48)
  Technical Teams Reports for P2K authored by Cowles, Boggess, Dimock, Tom Young, Donna Taber and others
- Evaluation of Database Systems/Informix Selection, 1995-1996 (Box 48)
- Evaluation of Application Development Environments, 1995 (Box 48)
- Cornell OIT Technologies Committee - Information Technologies Reports (Box 48)
  - Technologies Framework v 0.8, 1990 - 1995
  - Technologies Framework v 2.0, 1995 - 1997
- A Response to the Technologies Framework (Kevin Saunders ) (Box 48)
- Information Technologies 1995-1997 A Cornell University Perspective, 1992 (Box 48)
  Bob Cowles presented at SHARE Europe
- STOP Projects Document and Misc info, 1993-1994 (Box 48)
- Project STOP: Information Access Architecture, 1994 (Box 48)
- STOP Presentation at IR Quarterly Review (Bob Cowles), 1993-07 (Box 48)
- A note from the Director - Ten Years of Excellence in Computational Science, 1995-1996 (Box 48)
  CTC Tenth Anniversary Mal Kalos
- Theory Center - Symposium on "Supercomputing: The Next 50 years", 1991 (Box 48)
  Includes NSF Supercomputing Centers 1990 glossy
  Grand Challenges - High Performance Computing and Communications Supplement to the Presidents FY 1992 Budget
- CNSF - Smart Node Advisory Commitee Meeting, 1991-06 (Box 48)
- Evolving IT and Cornell - CU and DEC (Kampas), 1994-04 (Box 48)
- CITnet - Memos, issues with Proteon by Cogger, etc, 1988-1990 (Box 48)
- CCS/CIT Staff - Comings/Goings, 1980 - 1999 (Box 48)
- CCS/CIT Staff Directories, Service Providers, Org Chart, 1980 - 1999 (Box 48)
- CCS/CIT Staff Kudos, Accomplishments, etc, 1980 - 1999 (Box 48)
- P2K - High level Documents - Organization, Objectives, Structure, etc, 1994-1997 (Box 48)
- P2K - Team Documents, 1994-1997 (Box 48)
- P2K - Steering Group Documents/Minutes, 1994-1997 (Box 48)
- P2K - Technology Issues, etc, 1994-97 (Box 48)
- P2K - Budget, Financing, Costing and Benefits, 1994-97 (Box 48)
- P2K - Application Descriptions, requirements, plans, 1994-97 (Box 48)
- Strategic Planning - different initiatives (Cecilia Cowles), 1993-1996 (Box 48)
- Computing/Information Technology Planning Initiatives, 1993-1996 (Box 48)
  Merten Study, College Studies, 2001 Committee Report, CIT reports Supporting materials, etc. all contributed by Cecilia Cowles
- Services Division Buzz, 1990-1999 (Box 48)
  Plans, Memos, Ideas, Services Committee, etc
- Network Resources - Telecomm Transfer, Organization, UTP Ethernet, 1990-1992 (Box 48)
  SLIP, LANs, Local Access, etc
- CR (CSARS) Designated Income Projections, 1992-1994 (Box 48)
- Software AG Training Materials - Application Development, 1993 (Box 48)
- START Strategic Technology and Architecture Resource Team, 1992 (Box 48)
- Final Report - Market Research on PC Repair Services (student project), 1991 (Box 48)
- Understanding the Client and Consulting tracking reports, 1991 (Box 48)
- Publication Planning and Pubs Materials, 1989 (Box 48)
- Leftover 1970s Misc materials including letter from Ken Wilson Structured Walk-Throughs - A Project Management Tool - IBM, 1973 (Box 48)
- Viruses over the years - Misc notes, 1980 (Box 48)
- Langmuir as NYSEG backup, 1993 (Box 48)
- CIT/CR Planning, 1990 (Box 48)
- Files from Dick Cogger on CORVUS, PINCnet, Network Planning, etc, 1988 (Box 48)
- Operations - Reports, Network, Benchmarks, Tapes, Docutech, 1988 (Box 48)
- Remote 3270 Support (with breakdown of access by line type, 1989 (Box 48)
- Turning Data into Information - Data Warehousing in CIT, 1995 (Box 48)
- CUSS - Cornell Unix Systems Administrators Support Group, 1992 (Box 48)
- CR Budgets, Space, Networks and Buzz, 1988 (Box 48)
- Ops/Dave Pulleyn and JWR Issues, Correspondence, etc, 1986-1988 (Box 48)
- Admin Systems Disaster Contingency Plan (Draft), 1994 (Box 48)
- Unix Product Plan and Using DEC Equipment, 1989-1990 (Box 48)
- Sr Mgmt Presentations - Pubs, Word Processing, Public WorkStations, 1989 (Box 48)
- PeopleSoft Product Deliverables Update, 1996 (Box 48)
  Coopers and Lybrand Draft Support Proposal after Implementation
- PC/Jim Doolittle and JWR Issues, Correspondence, etc, 1985 (Box 49)
- PC/Jim Doolittle and JWR Issues, Correspondence, etc (1), 1986 (Box 49)
- PC/Jim Doolittle and JWR Issues, Correspondence, etc(2), 1986 (Box 49)
- PC/Jim Doolittle and JWR Issues, Correspondence, etc, 1987 (Box 49)
- PC/Jim Doolittle and JWR Issues, Correspondence, etc, 1987-1988 (Box 49)
- Systems/Tom Boggess and JWR Issues, etc, 1987-1988 (Box 49)
- Distributed Computing, Open Systems, VM and IBM Cambridge Lab, 1990-1999 (Box 49)
- EZ-Remote Product Brief (Draft), 1990-1999 (Box 49)
- Project Mandarin (collection of project documents), 1993-03 (Box 49)
- Project Mandarin (publication on background, joining, etc), 1994-07 (Box 49)
- Project Mandarin -CIT, 1994-07 (Box 49)
- Project Mandarin - Frequently Asked Questions, 1995 (Box 49)
- Project Mandarin - General Information, 1995-09 (Box 49)
- Project Mandarin - Product Catalog, 1995-09 (Box 49)
- Project Mandarin -Installing and Testing Server Software, 1996-01 (Box 49)
- Project Mandarin - Membership Handbook, 1996-04 (Box 49)
- Apple Technology - Blueprint for the Decade, 1991 (Box 49)
- Apple Technology - Client/Server Development Guide, 1992 (Box 49)
- Apple Technology - A Technical Introduction to VITAL, 1994 (Box 49)
- Introduction to VITAL - Designing IS for the 1990s, 1992 (Box 49)
- Rewriting Mainframe Applications for a Distributed Computing Environment, 1993-09 (Box 49)
  R. D. Cowles Alpha Presentation at CU developed for the Institute .for Advanced Professional Studies
- Rewriting Mainframe Applications for a Distributed Computing Environment, 1993-11 (Box 49)
  R. D. Cowles Beta Version developed for the Institute .for Advanced Professional Studies
- Design Options for Developing World Wide Web Applications - CIT, 1995-10 (Box 49)
- Admin. Info. Systems Strategic Review - Duesing, 1994 (Box 49)
- CU Administrative Information Systems Review by J. Michael Duesing, 1995 (Box 49)
- Penn PRINTOUT Vol. 12:4, 1996-03 (Box 49)
  ENIAC, Feb 14, 1946, The Birth of the Information Age
- ADSPAC - Review of Adspac by Members (Rogers/Rudan), 1995 (Box 49)
- Rates, Fund Transfers (library), Benchmarks, etc, 1980-1989 (Box 49)
- Theory Center, International Supercomputing Alliance, 1990 (Box 49)
  Brochures from PUC Rio and ITESM, Monterrey, Mexico
- IR 1991-92 Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 49)
- IR 1992-93 Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 49)
- IR Strategic Planning for Administrative Information Systems (Koehler, Lynn and Rogers), 1991 (Box 49)
- Electronic Mail, 1989-1990 (Box 49)
  A User's Guide to Electronic Mail (Ricemail on Mainframes)
- Getting Started with Electronic Mail, 1990 (Box 49)
  Ricemail with different terminals and connectivity
- Getting Started with VMS (2) with different Micros/Emulators, 1990 (Box 49)
- CMS Timesharing - Factors for Upgrading - Tom Boggess, 1991 (Box 49)
- SHARE Materials - Reports and Letters - from Cecilia Cowles, 1985-1986 (Box 49)
- Getting Started with CMS (2) with different Micros/Emulators, 1990 (Box 49)
- Getting Started with IBM PS/2 and with Macintosh Computers, 1990 (Box 49)
- Introductory Guide - Using the IBM Computer at Cornell, 1982 (Box 49)
  A new approach faculty written docs - Trochim and Kirk from Hum Ec
- OCS Users Manual by Martha Czerwinski (first published in 1967), 1969 (Box 49)
- A Preliminary Financial Study of Six Alternate Student Information, 1975 (Box 49)
  Systems by Mark Mara and William Turner for Henry Vaughan
- OCS Newsletters - extra copies, 1970-1974 (Box 50)
- CCS/CIT Bulletin - extra copies, 1984-1989 (Box 50)
- CIT Briefly (successor to Bulletin) - extra copies, 1989 - 1994 (Box 50)
- Inside CIT Volumes 1 and 2 - extra copies, 1990-1991 (Box 50)
- Inside CIT Volumes 3 and 4 - extra copies, 1992-1993 (Box 50)
- Document Sharing Project Planning Group - Common Solutions, 1995 (Box 50)
  Group - Cecilia Cowles
- Document Sharing Project Planning Group - Common Solutions, 1995 (Box 50)
  Group - Background Materials - Cecilia Cowles
- Dairy Records Processing Lab (DRPL) 360/40 installation and correspondence re cooperation and getting their 1401, 1966 (Box 51)
- Estimated Operating Expenses for the 360/67 by JWR, 1966 (Box 51)
- Usage Statistics B220 and CDC1604 (CORC Processing), 1962-1966 (Box 51)
- Computer Charge Rates, Rate Policies, Comparisons with others NACUBO materials, 1964-1965 (Box 51)
- Computer Rates and Policies - first use of Allocated Funds and fully supervised ops and differential rates, 1965 (Box 51)
- Reports on Grants and Contracts from Coordinator of Research, 1964-1965 (Box 51)
- Control Data - Correspondence, Contracts, (new Card Reader), 1963 (Box 51)
- CORC Records - Processing Volumes, Courses, etc, 1963-1964 (Box 51)
- CDC 1604 Installation: Floor Layout and Templates, Raised Floor also letters from Humphreys and Muller on assignments/needs, 1963 (Box 51)
- Proposal to NIH for Computing Services for Health-Related Research By R. W. Conway seeking $1,872,954 for 1967 to 1972, 1966 (Box 51)
- Formation of OCS - Report (R. W. Conway ), 1966 (Box 51)
- Ag College Computing Needs/Proposal for Computing Services Group, 1966 (Box 51)
- Letters on I/O requirements for incoming 360/67 (Conway file), 1966 (Box 51)
- Cornell Computing Center - Usage Reports, Billing/Income Reports, Income/Expense Reports. IBM650/Burroughs220/CDC 1604, 1956 - 1964 (Box 51)
- Physical Biology - Vet School; Proposal to HEW for IBM 1800 System, 1966 (Box 51)
- Computer Study - Backup materials from vendors, etc., 1965 (Box 51)
- Correspondence F.A.Long, J.A Perkins (CU Pres) to Finger Lakes area schools and colleges re computing, 1966 (Box 51)
- FLCCC - Finger Lakes Colleges Computing Center - correspondence, etc, 1966 (Box 51)
- FLCCC - Support materials for NSF Proposal, 1966 (Box 51)
- FLCCC - Proposal to NSF (Rudan/1966) and Supplement (Conway/1967), 1966-1967 (Box 51)
- A Study of Regional Computer Networks by Weingarten, Nielsen, Whitely and Weeg with partial support from NSF, 1973-02 (Box 51)
- Reports, etc Cornell Computing Center to Formation of OCS, 1965-1966 (Box 51)
  Conway, Rudan, Peterson, and Long (Long on major changes in June '65)
- Changes in Financial Condition and Outlook 1974-1977, 1978-02 (Box 51)
  Update of the 1975 Weiss Committee Report
- Cornell Statistical Computing Newsletter, 1970-1972 (Box 51)
- Proposal to Expand User Services - undated but presumably, 1973-1974 (Box 51)
  Ad Hoc Committee of the Faculty Council
- IBM Selectric Typewriter Manuals, 1982 (Box 51)
- RUN, the COMMODORE 64/128 Users Guide from Duane Lukosavich, 1988-03 (Box 51)
- Buchan Industries - Catalog Racks, Binders, 1988-08 (Box 51)
- Wright Line - Filing and eferencing Systems for data processing media, 1977-04 (Box 51)
- MiSCO - Computer Supplies and Accessories, 1988-07-1988-08 (Box 51)
- Candle Computer Report, 1987-07-1987-08 (Box 51)
- Moore Business Products Catalog, 1988 (Box 51)
  Fall/Winter
- Moore Business Products Catalog, 1989 (Box 51)
  Summer
- Inmac - Personal Computer Catalog, 1989-01, 1989-09 (Box 51)
- UARCO - Quality Computer Supplies and Continuous Forms Holiday Ed., 1987 (Box 51)
- Global Computer Supplies, 1987-08 (Box 51)
- Wilson Jones Computer and Office Products, 1989-01 (Box 51)
- Computer Hotline (Used Equipment), 1987-10 (Box 51)
- Annual Reports
- OCS Annual Reports (extra Copies; not all years), 1970-1979 (Box 52)
- Computer Services - Operations Report for FY 1977-78, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
- Computer Services - Administrative Production Units Report FY 1977-78, 1977-1978 (Box 52)
- CIT Operations Annual Report, 1988-1989 (Box 52)
- CIT Operations Annual Report, 1989- 1990 (Box 52)
- CIT Operations Annual Report, 1990-1991 (Box 52)
- CIT Operations Annual Report, 1991-1992 (Box 52)
- CIT Support Services Admin Data Processing Annual Report, 1981-1982 (Box 52)
- CIT Support Services Admin Data Processing Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 52)
- CIT Support Services Admin Data Processing Annual Report, 1983-1984 (Box 52)
- CIT Production Support Services Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 52)
- CIT Production Support Services Annual Report, 1987-1988 (Box 52)
- CIT Production Support Services Annual Report, 1988-1989 (Box 52)
- CIT Production Support Services Annual Report, 1989-1990 (Box 52)
- CIT Ops/DE Annual Report, 1994-1995 (Box 52)
- CIT Ops/DE Annual Report, 1995-1996 (Box 52)
- CR Quarterly Reviews, 1990-1992 (Box 52)
- CIT Annual Reports, 1988 -1989 to 1991-1992 (Box 52)
- CIT Annual Reports, 2000-2001 to 2004-2005 (Box 52)
- CIT Annual Reports, 2006-2007 (Box 52)
- Annual and other Reports
- CISER Annual Reports, 1981-1982 to 2002 (Box 53)
- Mariann Carpenter - CISER file on Policies, Procedures, Notes, etc., 1980 - 1999 (Box 53)
- CIT Division Priorities, 1991 (Box 53)
- Miscellaneous Divisional Quarterly Reviews, 1992 (Box 53)
- CIT Services Division Q - Reviews, 1992 (Box 53)
- PC/DE 3rd Quarter Report and Annual Laser Printing Report, 1992-1994 (Box 53)
- Computing and Information Science - Final Task Force Report, 1999, 2001, 2002 (Box 53)
- Forefronts - Theory Center Publication plus 1 Backgrounds, 1980-1997 (Box 53)
  Incomplete from 9/85 (vol. 1, no. 5) to 1997 (vol. 12, no. 2)
- A National Computing Initiative - The Agenda for Leadership, 1987 (Box 53)
  Report of the Panel on Research Issues in Large-scale Computational Science and Engineering
- Grand Challenges - High Performance Computing and Communications, 1992 (Box 53)
  The FY 1992 U. S. Research and Development Program
- Grand Challenges - High Performance Computing and Communications, 1993 (Box 53)
  The FY 1993 U. S. Research and Development Program
- The Federal High Performance Computing Program, 1989 (Box 53)
  Executive Off. of the President, Of.f of Science and Technology Policy
- Program Plan to the National Science Foundation FY92, 1992 (Box 53)
  Cornell Theory Center
- NSF Supercomputing Centers, 1991 (Box 53)
- Supercomputing for the 1990s: A shared responsibility Higher Education and Technology Committee of the National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1989 (Box 53)
- KSR Technology Background - Kendall Square Research, 1992 (Box 53)
- Blackboard Folder including emails from CU/CTC staff plus Jay Walker, Theglobe.com,Jeffrey Hawkins of Handspring, 1990-1999 (Box 53)
- CCS to CIT Organization - Goals, Mission, Organization Charts, 1988 (Box 53)
- Technologies Committee- Minutes, emails, 1991 (Box 53)
- Mainframe Stories, Statistics, Upgrades, 1990-1999 (Box 53)
- CR - Computer Resources Miscellaneous, 1990-1999 (Box 53)
- Magazines, Articles, etc., Technology, 1990-1999 (Box 53)
- Electronic Mail (VM based comparisons and usage), 1988 (Box 53)
- Micros and MOS - Student Notices by Nancy Flynn, Tom Hughes, 1987-1988 (Box 53)
- MERIT Computer Network, Management and Operations of the NSFNET Backbone Network - Proposal to NSF plus 2 glossies, 1987 (Box 54)
- Ad Hoc Task Force on Research Computing, 1994 (Box 54)
- CIT Cost Transfer Mechanisms, Business Modelling, 1989,1992 (Box 54)
- Financial Restructuring - 2 CUBIT presentations, 1990, 1991 (Box 54)
- Emails - IR Council/Mgmt/Policies/People, 1994-1996 (Box 54)
- Emails - IR Projects/IVY+, 1994-1996 (Box 54)
- Emails - IR JWR's term, Hiring new Director Mohrmann, 1994-1996 (Box 54)
- Emails - IR Organization Items, Transform IR, 1993-1995 (Box 54)
- Emails - Helen Mohrmann, 1995-2000 (Box 54)
- Academic Computing at CU - Creating an Effective Public and Personal Academic Comp Environment, 2003-09 (Box 54)
- Actuate - Reporting Tool for PeopleSoft HR/Payroll, 1998-1999 (Box 54)
- GATED, 1980-1990 (Box 54)
- Network Protocols TCP/IP, SLIP, 1990-1999 (Box 54)
- Network Technologies, 1990-1999 (Box 54)
- NSFNet, NYSERNet, Bitnet, 1990-1999 (Box 54)
- Kerberos, Sidecar, Network Security, Internic, CERT, 1990-1999 (Box 54)
- Bulletin Boards/Electronic Conferencing, 1990-1999 (Box 54)
- Deep Blue - IBM Research - Computer Chess, 1990-1999 (Box 54)
- CR - Computer Resources Miscellaneous, 1990-1999 (Box 54)